<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Themes on Prestashop Developer Documentation</title>
    <link>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Themes on Prestashop Developer Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 11:07:21 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Guidelines and coding standards</title>
      <link>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/guidelines/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/guidelines/</guid>
      <description>Guidelines and coding standards Compatibility PHP Code Your PHP code should be compatible with the following versions:
 PrestaShop 1.7.0  ~ 1.7.3  : at least PHP 5.4 PrestaShop 1.7.4  : at least PHP 5.6  HTML / CSS / Javascript Your HTML/CSS/JS code should work with at least:
 IE9+ Edge Firefox 45 Chrome 29.  Mobile-wise:
 iOS 8.4 Android Browser 4.4  Standards General Use spaces for indentation in every language (PHP, HTML, CSS, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Migrating from PrestaShop 1.6</title>
      <link>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/migration_from_16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/migration_from_16/</guid>
      <description>Migrating from PrestaShop 1.6 PrestaShop 1.7 introduces a totally reworked theme system from version 1.6, with the goal of making PrestaShop upgrades easier, and making it easier and faster to create a brand new theme.
The huge change to the theme system means that there is no easy way to migrate your PrestaShop 1.6 theme to PrestaShop 1.7.
When using the automatic upgrade from PrestaShop 1.6 to 1.7, your theme will be switched to the new default theme, called &amp;ldquo;Classic&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RTL support</title>
      <link>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/rtl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://devdocs.prestashop.com/1.7/themes/rtl/</guid>
      <description>RTL support PrestaShop supports RTL (Right-to-left) themes natively.
RTL stylesheets There are two ways of customizing your theme for RTL: either by adding an override file that is only loaded for RTL languages, or by using completely different version of the theme&amp;rsquo;s stylesheets.
CSS override file PrestaShop will try to load a css file named rtl.css after your theme&amp;rsquo;s ones when displayed in an RTL language. You can use this file to place any style override you need for RTL.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>